

# REYNALDO R. DALOG

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

#48 MABINI ST., DISTRICT 1, CAUAYAN CITY ISABELA, PHILIPPINES 3305

AVAILABILITY: I CAN START FOR WORK AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.

# CONTACT

+639213903864

http://reynaldodalog.com va.reynaldodalog@gmail.com www.facebook.com/reynaldodalog

# **EDUCATION**

Isabela State University BS - Information Technology Jun 2003 - Apr 2007

## **SKILLS**

HTML5 - CSS3

...25 0000

Wordpress

Elementor Divibuilder

WPBakery

Figma

Photoshop

Adobe UX

# **ABOUT ME**

I have 10 years of working experience as an I.T professional. I have a considerable amount of experience in computer hardware. I also have been exposed in various software applications such as Photoshop, illustrator, Canva, Affinity Designer and Wordpress for Web Designing.

In the years I have been working I gained and mastered numerous skills such as configuring computer system and network, and Graphic and multimedia designing.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Website Designer**

Jan 2020- October 2021

**MML Digital Marketing** 

Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients, Testing and improving the design of the website, Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices, Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards, Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients, Working with different content management systems, Communicating design ideas using user flows, process flows, site maps and wireframes, Incorporating functionalities and features into websites, Designing sample pages including colors and fonts, Preparing design plans and presenting the website structure.

#### **Website Developer**

**QRX** Digital

February 2020 - May 2020

Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients, Testing and improving the design of the website, Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices, Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards, Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients.

### Freelance Web - Graphic Designer

Virtualahan

Apr 2018 - May 2020

Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients, Testing and improving the design of the website, Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices, Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards, Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients.

#### **System - Administrator**

Cauayan Medical Specialists Hospital

June 2013 - April 2018

Maintain and Troubleshoot Computer System and local Network, Develop Hospital Website, Install and update Hospital Information System, Troubleshoot and Install Computer Hardware and Software, Design Graphic and Media Materials, Always Securing Back up and Restoration process every 3 hours operation.

## **EDUCATIONAL ATTAINMENT**

# **Bachelor of Science in Information Technology**

College

Isabela State University – Cauayan Campus San Fermin Cauayan City, Isabela Jun 2003 - Apr 2007

**High School** 

Isabela Colleges Cauayan City, Isabela (1999 – 2003)

**Elementary** 

Cauayan South Central School Cauayan City, Isabela (1990 – 1996)

## CERTIFICATION

#### Virtualahan

Wordpress Masterclass - Elementor Setup Aug 2020

#### **UDEMY**

HTML and CSS for Beginners - Build a Website & Launch ONLINE Sept. 24, 2020

## **UDEMY**

Learn Responsive Web Development from Scratch Oct 02, 2020

#### **UDEMY**

Complete Wordpress Theme Development Course Feb 27, 2021

## SEMINARS ATTENDED

## 3rd Bizbox IT-Summit

Bayanihan Center Hall A.Pioneer St., Pasig, Metro Manila Jan 24, 2017

## **CCNA Collaboration Voice Over IP and Video**

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

## **CCNA Security ASA Firewall VPN and GRE Tunneling**

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

# Windows Server 2012 Clustering and Windows Deployment Services

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

# VMWare Sphere and vCloud Director

SM Megatrade Hall Meeting Room B 5th Floor SM Mega Mall B Ortigas Center, Mandaluyong City, Philippines Feb 11, 2017

# **REFERENCES:**

# Raquel J. Gammad

Acting Branch Head Producers Savings Bank Corporation

Tel.No.: +639956455835

 ${\bf Email: raquel.gammad@producersbank.com.ph}$ 

Relationship: client

## Aldrin G. Coloma

Chief Executive Officer Latreia Prime Solution

LEI Partners LLC / Truckload Logistics

Tel.No.: Phil: +639776284625 USA: +17047544325

Email: aldrincoloma7@gmail.com acoloma@leipartners.net

Relationship: Client